appbackr.com 2016-04-22

# ​

Privacy Policy
Your Privacy Rights. Welcome to appbackr.com (the “Site” or “Apps”), a website and mobile
applications operated by appbackr​   ®​Inc. (“appbackr,” “we,” or “us”). The Site and Apps which
provide access to data about apps through its Index and related product offerings, along with
apps where users can share apps and app reviews. We understand that your privacy is
important. With this in mind, we have created and posted this privacy policy that describes our
collection, use, and disclosure practices. Your use of the Site and the services offered through
the Site (the “Services”) constitute your acknowledgement and acceptance of our privacy
practices. If you are not comfortable with any of the practices we describe in this privacy
policy, please do not use the Site or the Services.
THE SITE AND THE SERVICES ARE HOSTED IN THE UNITED STATES. IF YOU ARE A
USER ACCESSING THE SITE OR SERVICES FROM THE EUROPEAN UNION, ASIA, OR
ANY OTHER REGION WITH LAWS OR REGULATIONS GOVERNING PERSONAL DATA
COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE THAT DIFFER FROM UNITED STATES LAWS,
PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT THROUGH YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SITE OR THE
SERVICES, YOU ARE TRANSFERRING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE
UNITED STATES AND YOU CONSENT TO THAT TRANSFER. ADDITIONALLY, YOU
UNDERSTAND THAT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE PROCESSED IN
COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING
PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN IN YOUR
COUNTRY.
A Note About Children. The Site is not designed to attract children under the age of 18 and
we do not intentionally gather any information about visitors who are under the age of 18.
The Ways We Collect Information
Personal Information. “Personal Information" means information about you that is personally
identifiable, like your name, address, email address, or phone number, as well as other
non­public information that is associated with this personal information. The Personal
Information we obtain about you is information you knowingly provide to us or otherwise
authorize us to collect, including but not limited to your device, its location, its carrier
information, and the apps on your phone. If you register with us and create an “Account” to
gain access to the the Site, you will provide us with your name and email address and select
a password.
We may collect and store the following Personal Information:
1. Your name;
2. Your contact information (e.g., your address, email address, and telephone number),
gender, and Stripe or PayPal account name;

3. Transactional information based on your activities on the Site (such as the apps you use;
share; and store on your device, including ones that you may have deleted);
4. Information about an application you are attempting to sell in the case of the Marketplace;
5. Your biography, as written by you, your login ID for Twitter and LinkedIn and your personal
URL (1, 3, 4, and 5, collectively, “Application Information”); and
6. Information and communications relating to dispute resolution, correspondence through the
Site, and correspondence sent to us. If you are a developer of applications, we may receive
information from Apple, Inc., (“Apple”), Google, Inc. (“Google”), Samsung Electronics, Inc.
(“Samsung”), Amazon, Inc. (“Amazon”), and others about the development and sale of such
applications, which we will consider Application Information.
We may also attempt to verify certain aspects of your Personal Information with Apple,
Google and other third­party service providers. In the event we receive additional information
about you from such third parties, any such information disclosed or otherwise learned by us,
excluding iTunes Information, shall be considered Personal Information for the purposes of
this Agreement and not Application Information, regardless of the type or character of
information. Anonymous information “Anonymous Information” means information that is not
linked to Personal Information and does not enable contact with any identifiable person. As
you use the Site or the Services, certain Anonymous Information may also be passively
collected and stored on our server logs, such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type,
and access times. We also store a small text file called a “Cookie” on your computer to store
your login information (if any) and your personal preferences for the Services. We may use
both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies
(which stay on your computer until you delete them). One of the primary purposes of Cookies
is to provide a convenience feature to save you time by telling the Web server that you have
returned to a specific page. While you will still be able to use the Site if you disable Cookies in
your browser, you will need to log in each time you visit the Site.
The Ways We Use Information. We will use your Personal Information to:
• Administer your Account;
• Respond to your requests, resolve disputes, and/or troubleshoot problems;
• Verify your compliance with your obligations in the Site’s Terms of Service, the Developer
Agreement and the Wholesale Purchase Agreement (if applicable) (collectively, the “User
Agreements”);
• Provide you with Services and customer support;
• Collect fees and distribute revenue;
• Prevent potentially prohibited activities, and enforce our User Agreements;
• Improve the quality of the Site and the Services; and
• Communicate with you and provide you with other information that may be useful or
interesting to you. We will send you Service­related announcements upon the occurrence of
certain events and when we believe it is necessary to do so. You may not opt out of these
communications, which are not promotional in nature, but if you do not wish to receive these
announcements, you have the option of terminating your affiliation with appbackr by

contacting us at ​support@appbackr.com​        . We may use your Anonymous Information internally
to improve our internal operations or software, tailor web content to your interests, and
automatically log you into the Site on subsequent visits.
The Ways We Disclose Information. We may disclose certain Personal Information:
• To other appbackr members, in the form of Application Information;
• To other appbackr members who are using the Site, including iTunes Information, Google
Play information, and data collected from your phone if using our App and your contact
information;
• To third party vendors who help us provide the Services or the Site;
• To third parties to whom you ask us to send Personal Information;
• To a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common
control (collectively, “Affiliates”), in the event we have such Affiliates in the future, in which
case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy;
• To a company that merges with us, acquires us, or purchases our assets, in which case
such company may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy
Policy; or
• If we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) resolve disputes,
investigate problems, or enforce our User Agreements; (b) comply with relevant laws or to
respond to requests from law enforcement or other government officials relating to
investigations or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose Personal
Information without subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (c) protect and defend our rights
or property or the rights and property of you or third­parties.
We may disclose Anonymous Information to:
• Third party vendors who may help us enhance or provide appbackr or Services; or
• To third parties whom you ask us to send Personal Information.
Information You Share on the Site. Because appbackr maintains a community­oriented
Marketplace, it is important that buyers have sufficient information about developers in order
to consider purchases. Also, the Company’s Apps involve sharing apps which necessitate the
collection and sharing of certain information about which apps you have stored, your location,
and other personal information. Certain Application Information is required in order to
participate in and receive certain Services but other Application Information you may provide
to us is optional. You are welcome to share as much information about yourself as you think is
necessary and appropriate. We will display on the Site any Application Information you
provide to us and we may also display certain iTunes Information and information from
Google Play and other such stores as well.
We may provide Account holders on our Site with the opportunity to communicate with you
through an in­browser or in­App message box. If you respond to any in­browser or in­App
message, you may be providing the recipient your email address or other personally
identifiable information such as your WhatsApp or Twitter identification. Through this

communication, Account holders may request additional information from you. Such sharing
of information is entirely your choice, and you share this information at your own discretion.
How You Can Update or Delete Your Information. You can see, review, and change most of
your Personal Information by registering as a member on the Site. You must promptly update
your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. Upon your request, we will close your
account and remove your Application Information from view as soon as reasonably possible,
in accordance with applicable law. We do retain Personal Information from closed accounts to
comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot
problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our User Agreements, and take other actions
otherwise permitted by law.
Information Disclosed to Third Parties. This document addresses only the use and disclosure
of information we collect from and/or about you. If you disclose your information to others,
including to other appbackr members, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of
the information you disclose to them. We do not control the privacy policies of third parties,
and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. The Site
may contain links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us. We have no
control over, do not review, and are not responsible for the privacy policies of or content
displayed on other such websites. When you click on such a link, you will leave the Site and
go to another site. During this process, another entity may collect Personal Information or
Anonymous Information from you. Please review the other site’s privacy practices before
engaging or trusting that site with your personal information.
Changes to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is subject to revision from time to time,
and revisions will apply prospectively and not retroactively. We will post any revised version of
the Privacy Policy on this page. If we make any material changes to it, we will also send you
notice thereof to the last email address you have provided to us. Any amended Privacy Policy
will be effective: thirty (30) calendar days after posting for then­current members, and upon
posting for any persons who create an Account after such posting. Any changes to this
Privacy Policy may affect our use or disclosure of Personal Information collected prior to the
changes. If you do not agree to any of the changes, you must notify us prior to the effective
date of the changes that you wish to terminate your appbackr membership. Continued use of
our Services following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such
changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.
Contact Us. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please
contact us by sending an email to ​   support@appbackr.com​     .
This Privacy Policy was last revised: May 1, 2015.
